

PROFILE

I have motivational 3 years plus experience in programming, and Teaching field. Want to give my best contribution to the organization or company, keep developing myself through learning method and want to share my knowledge to other to gain more knowledge.

I had participated some of programming contest like Skill competition 2017 where I presented a project for blindman.

I want to share my one project where I did different type of authentication systems. This project basically for a manage a whole Super-shop.

CONTACT

PHONE: +971 05 451 42219

ADDRESS: House 39, Block 18-B, Al-

Satwa, Dubai, UAE

Portfolio Link:

https://shafilbd.github.io/

EMAIL:

shafilahmedc@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Teaching Reading Books Machine Learning Playing Guitar

SHAFIL AHMED CHOWDHURY

Web Developer

EDUCATION

School: Feni G. A. Academy High School

January 2009 - February 2014

CGPA- 4.75 (out of 5.00) **Department-** Science **Note:** Attested from UAE Embassy of Bangladesh

College: Feni Computer Institute August 2014 – September 2018

CGPA- 3.48(out of 4.00) Department- Data Networking and Technology

Note: Attested from UAE Embassy of Bangladesh

WORK EXPERIENCE

NetTech247 LLC – Full Stack Developer 03 February- present This is Software company. They have online portal to give the services to the client in whole Dubai. I worked there as a Full Stack developer to create their projects an maintain other project of them and solving bugs are main Job.

Blockchain Innovation and Investment Summit- IT Specialist September 2019– November 2019

This is the Blockchain company in Dubai. The Main Responsibility of mine was maintaining their all it supports and develop their website, software. Beside to contact with foreign clients to know them about our upcoming events and develop their online payment method system.

Soft tech Technology Ltd - Junior web developer

June 2018 –September 2019

Basically, I handle most designing part of software and websites other created report and presentation for the projects.

SKILLS

